这是您的账单
Here's your check.
并在此对您整个用餐体验致以歉意
Sorry about the entire experience.
得麻烦你手伸过来拿了
You're gonna have to take it the rest of the way.
我去年睡落枕了
I slept funny last year.
我刚好还是个按摩师呢
You know, I happen to be a massage therapist,
而且还刚好一穷二白 要不这样吧
and I happen to be broke, so what do you say
我帮你把脖子弄好 当做小费行吗
I get that crick out of your neck as your tip?
我好怀念我有骨气直接拒绝的时候
I miss being able to just say no.
稍等 我得向我贫穷界的前辈请教一下这事
Hold on, I have to run this by a person who's been poor longer.
有件惨事 那男的想用按摩来抵小费
Sadly, that guy over there is offering me a massage as a tip.
更惨的是 我真心在考虑
Sadly-er, I'm considering it.
最惨的是 当时那个老太捶我奶子一拳
Sadly-est, you were here when that old woman punched me
然后要求找零的那会 你亲眼目睹了不是吗
in the breast and then asked for change, right?
我们就是这么悲催
We're not doing great.
世上绝对有人比你俩更惨更可怜
There's got to be somebody doing worse than you two.
比如去年被遗忘在火星上的那男人[电影]
Like that guy who got left on Mars last year.
姑娘们 提问
Question, girls.
我想要设计更健康的菜单
I'm making a healthier menu.
我应该写上不含反式脂肪吗
Should I advertise no trans fat,
这是这样会听起来像不让查兹·波诺进
or does that sound like I'm trying to keep out Chaz Bono?
现在没空 阿憨 我预约了做按摩
Not now, Han, I have a massage scheduled.
"假装"在工作的压力
All the stress of acting like you're working
终于压垮你的小身板了吗
starting to get to you?
她一人"得到" 我"鸡鸡"升天
I just had what she's having.
麦克斯 你现在忙吗
Max, are you busy right now?
-当然不 我在上班 -那就好
- No, I'm at work. - Cool.
我要召集大家开员工会议
I'm gonna call a staff meeting.
想当年我是打给司机[召集]
I used to call my driver to
让他在我看电视剧时去拿寿司外卖
pick up sushi during Gilmore Girls,
而我现在是在餐厅召集开员工会议
but now I call staff meetings at a diner.
只有我可以在这餐厅里召集开员工会议
Only I can call staff meetings at the diner.
是我这工作的亮点之一
It's one of the perks of the job.
是我这工作最赞的点
Well, it's the perk of the job.
好啦 是还行
Well, it's okay.
这是我跟麦克斯要在小蛋糕窗口
The staff meeting is about the dessert bar
新开的甜品吧事务的员工会议
Max and I are opening in our cupcake window.
如果你真想要的话 阿憨 你来召集开会吧
If you want, Han, you can call the meeting,
但我觉得你不会可悲到
but I can't imagine you'd be petty enough
连这点小快乐都要从卡洛琳那里夺走
to take the thrill away from Caroline.
员工会议
Staff meeting!
你看 这就是
See, this is what happens
母猫不舔小猫 小猫身心不健全的样子
when the mother cat refuses to lick the runt.
我要检查一下我给你们每个人
Okay, so I'm checking on the dessert bar assignments
布置的任务
I gave everyone.
厄尔 你打电话给你亲戚
Earl, did you call your cousin
问酒供应商能不能给我们折扣的事了吗
at that liquor distributor about getting us a discount?
我为啥要打给他
Now, why would I call him?
我还欠他一万块加一个肾呢
I owe him $10,000 and a kidney.
所以就是"还没完成"
So that's a "Not yet."
我也还没做我的部分
I haven't done my thing, either.
卡洛琳 你从好莱坞拿到的钱
Caroline, with all your money from Hollywood,
你完全能付钱请别人做这些事情
you could pay other people to do this stuff...
还能帮某人的12年款雅力士换变速器
and also replace the transmission on a 2012 Yaris.
我们得所有的钱都省下来给甜品吧
We have to save all our movie money for the dessert bar.
而我的胸部居然没法帮我们搞到区域许可证呢
Believe it or not, my boobs can't get us zoning permits.
但它们成功让我们被赶出建筑师办公室
But they did get us kicked out of an architect's office.
奥列格 你跟你在市政厅里的人
Oleg, did you talk to your connection at City Hall
谈过加快审批我们酒水许可证的事了吗
about expediting our liquor license?
有啊 她跟我说"不许再从
Yes, she told me, "Don't ever sneak into my home
我浴室窗口溜进我家"
through the bathroom window again."
真是妙哉
Oh, this is rich.
现在你们俩终于知道我经营小生意
Now you two see some of the hell I go through
经过怎么样的地狱般磨难了吧
as a small business owner.
不 你会有地狱般的磨难是因为
No, you go through hell 'cause nobody wants to
没人想看你裆中的"小生意"
see your small business.
员工会议结束
Staff meeting over!
小员工会议
Small staff meeting.
麦克斯 你男朋友是个律师
Max, your boyfriend is a lawyer.
你今晚去他酒店的时候
When you're at his hotel tonight,
能请他帮忙看一下酒水许可证的申请表吗
can you ask him to look at our liquor license?
然后 你能倒满一冰桶的酒店小瓶洗发水
Also, could you fill an ice bucket with mini shampoos
然后带回家吗
and bring it home?
两件事都不行
No on both counts.
不许你找兰迪做法律咨询
You're not using Randy for legal advice.
而洗发水现在改成固定在墙上的壁挂式
And as for the shampoo, they switched to a pump bolted to the wall,
因为我上次太贪心了
'cause I was getting greedy.
兰迪
Hey, Randy.
你好啊 厄尔
Hey, Earl.
看到你昨晚在推特上发的抱怨文了
Saw your rant on Twitter last night.
我也同意
And I agree;
一间自重自爱的自助餐店雪碧怎么会缺货
what self-respecting Sizzler runs out of Sprite?
我写到推特上了吗
I put that on Twitter?
我还以为我是给我兄弟写了电邮呢
I thought I was writing an email to my brother.
你好啊 小美人
Hey there, beautiful.
我在想 我们今晚应该换点不一样的
So I thought we'd try something different tonight.
换你来上面吗
You on top?
我说的不是换我们整个权力结构
No, I'm not talking about changing our whole power dynamic.
我是指去你的公寓住
I'm talking about staying at your apartment.
所以你在下面吗
So, you on bottom?
毕竟那可是我的巢穴
'Cause that's where I live.
我是说认真的
No, really.
我们那个酒店房间就像是梦幻之地
We're living in a fantasy world, that hotel room.
我是指很香艳的梦幻之地
I mean, a really sexy fantasy world,
而且事后还有人帮我们打扫房间
with people cleaning up after us
还有个高中跟你同校的家政人员
and a maid who knew you from high school.
她看到我没死加全裸时简直吓呆了
Boy, was she surprised to see me naked and alive.
像我就每次都吓呆了
I know I always am.
麦克斯 我已经去过你公寓了啊
And Max, I've been to your apartment.
没那么糟啊
It wasn't that bad.
好吧 行 我们可以住我家
Uh, okay, fine. We can stay at my place.
但请自带一侦
But it's BYOC.
自己带一氧化碳侦测器
Bring your own carbon monoxide detector.
到啦
Well, here we are.
窟 温馨的贫民窟
Slum, sweet slum.
她每次走进这里都这么说
She says that every time she walks in here.
通常是为了吓走跑进我们厨房的吸毒毒虫
It's usually to scare the crack addict out of our kitchen.
艾伦 你在里面吗
Allen, are you here?
好啦 就是这样啦
All right, well, this is it.
你现在想做什么
What do you want to do now?
我们通常都是睡觉 这样死亡来得快一些
We usually go to sleep so death comes sooner.
你们别这样 这区区公寓我不在话下
You guys, I can handle an apartment.
别被我宽阔的肩膀 胡渣与喉结所迷惑
Don't let my broad shoulders, stubble, and Adam's apple confuse you;
我真的是纯爷们
I am, in fact, a man.
接下来我们正前方就是厨房
Coming up straight ahead is the kitchen.
但不说你也知道
But I don't have to tell you that.
因为你能闻到瓦斯的味道
You can smell the gas.
有趣小知识 这些纸巾其实不是真的纸
Fun fact: those paper towels you see aren't actually paper,
但绝对会致癌
but they do cause cancer.
我猜猜 是死神来敲门吗
Ooh, let me guess: the Grim Reaper?
错 死神都是周二跟周四晚来
No, the Grim Reaper comes on Tuesdays and Thursdays.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
还有兰迪迪
And Randy. Oh.
某人一直有在吃帅气药呢
Someone's been taking his handsome pills.
他们现在有做咀嚼片版本
Well, they make them in chewable now.
比以前容易吃下去
Makes it a lot easier.
兰迪来啦
Oh, Randy's here?
你好呀 兄弟
Hey, hey, hey, bro.
我们等会应该一起在楼上玩
We should hang upstairs later.
我们可以一起吃披萨然后看三级片
We can eat pizza and watch dirty movies.
不是外送加急 是变态加三级
It's not delivery; it's diporno.
确定一定以及肯定拒绝
That's a hard no.
姑娘们 我们有些东西想暂放你们家
Girls, we need to store some stuff in your place.
我跟奥列格要在公寓装婴儿保护措施
Oleg and I are baby-proofing our apartment.
我妈也为了我装了家庭婴儿保护措施
My mom baby-proofed our house for me.
在我们住的车上的方向盘加了方向盘锁
She put a club on the steering wheel.
在这个行李袋里 我放了...
So in this duffle bag, I have--
他要打开了
He's opening it!
兰迪 快闭上你的眼睛
Randy, close your eyes!
放轻松
Relax.
只是剑
It's just swords
跟性爱玩具罢了
and sex toys.
其中一个好像两者兼是啊
Oh, I think one of them's both.
你是在说我们的亚射王石中出剑吗
Are you referring to sex-calibur?
我好爱这一把
Oh, I love this one.
这把剑是我们用来演
This is the sword we used
"屌王柯南"时所用的道具
when we were playing Bonan the Barbarian.
而且你知道吗
And you know what?
把它们送给那些不那么"性运"的人 挺好的
It's good to give to the less sexually fortunate.
是的
Yeah.
这些性爱玩具就是给你的 卡洛琳
The sex toys are for you, Caroline.
我不缺 我刚享受完"按摩"
I'm good, I had a massage.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
厉害的忍者们都是这么吃贝果的
This is how all the great ninjas eat their bagels.
兰迪呢
Where's Randy?
他回去没过期牛奶
Did he go back to the land of not-expired milk,
与没过期蜂蜜之地了吗
and not-expired honey?
没 他比我想象中还坚强
No, he's stronger than I thought.
跟我在运动娱乐场里掰手腕的侏儒差不多强
Much like that little person I arm wrestled at Chelsea Piers.
我很爱这里
I love it here.
我刚洗了灰常棒的澡
I just took the grayest shower of my life.
你刚才是说"灰"常还是"非"常
Did you just say "grayest" or "greatest"?
我说的是"灰"
No, I said gray.
我不想说得太毒
I was being kind.
其实是大便色
It was brown.
来吧 剑砍贝果准备好了
All right, well, come on, your sword bagel is ready.
天啊 我还真的好想念做爱
God, I do miss having sex.
对了 那是怎么回....
Also, what is the deal with--
我操
Oh! God! Oh!
我踩到了让人很痛的东西
Ugh, I just stepped on something painful.
超级痛
Really painful!
地板上是有突出的钉子之类的吗
Is there a nail sticking up through the floor?
惨了 他踩到钉子·帕特里克·哈里斯
Oh no, he stepped on Nail Patrick Harris!
我忘了警告你有钉子了
Oh, I forgot to warn you about that stupid nail.
在那里很久了 我都习惯自动避开了
It's been there forever. I just know to avoid it by now.
大家都是啊 所以我们才叫他
Everyone does; that's why we named it
"钉子"·帕特里克·哈里斯
"Nail Patrick Harris."
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你看起来好像很痛啊
You look like you're in a lot of pain.
你想碰碰运气
Do you want to roll the dice
吃一颗从沙发里挖出来的随机药丸吗
with one of the pills in the couch?
我没事 没这么严重啦
I'm fine. It's not that bad.
把你的脚举起来 我看看伤口
Okay, well lift up your foot. Let me see.
天啊 天啊 天啊
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
兰迪
Randy?
这严重了吧
This is bad.
我们得带你去医淤安院看看
I think we have to take you to Hapitalito.
我一定是要失去意识了
Well, I must be losing consciousness.
你的话我听起来像胡言乱语
That sounded like gibberish.
没 你没听错 真的就是医淤安院
No, you heard me right, I said Hapitalito.
那是我们的医疗保险提供者
That's our healthcare provider.
是一个推着一推车邦迪的人
It's a guy with a shopping cart filled with Band-Aids,
而且里面大部分都是没用过的好货呢
and most of them aren't used.
麦克斯 我有医保
Max, I have insurance.
我觉得他那边不接受医疗保险
Well, I don't think he takes insurance,
如果你有旧的冻酸奶店的卡
but if you have old TCBY cards,
五张可以换"一次手术"呢
five is good for "Uno surgeria."
可能止血了
Well, maybe it stopped.
我是嘉丽 被泼了猪血的嘉丽
I'm Carrie! I'm Carrie at the prom!
卡洛琳 好啦 我们得去医院了
Caroline, come on, we have to go.
我已经浑身是血了 就让我自己死去吧
I'm already covered in blood. Just leave me to die.
冷静点好吗
Oh, calm down!
如果是我平常约会的那个等级的男人
If this had happened with any of my regular type of guys,
你现在已经差不多得丙肝了
you'd be halfway to Hep C right now.
救人啊 救人啦
Help! Help!
我的公寓想谋杀我男朋友
My apartment tried to kill my boyfriend!
他要死了
He's gonna die!
我不会死的 麦克斯
I'm not gonna die, Max.
不过我被你用药房塑料袋绑住的脚
Although, this CVS bag you tied around my foot
勒太近完全影响我的血液循环
has completely cut off the circulation.
而且袋子里那3米长的收据要跑进伤口了
And the ten-foot receipt's caught in the wound.
我的男朋友需要接受治疗
My boyfriend needs medical attention.
是咩
Oh, really?
我还以为他来是想买一套看起来精明干练
I thought he was here for a sensible pantsuit
价钱又合理的裤装的呢
at a reasonable price.
我认得你
Oh, I recognize you
我们上次来这里时你也在[第1季第16集]
from the last time we were in here.
我当时就不被你外表所吸引
I wasn't attracted to you then,
你这一次还加入了秃顶跟大胡子呢
but I see you've added balding and a beard to the mix.
呵呵 我也记得你呢
Ha, ha, I remember you too.
穿着超市货的恶魔
The devil wears Target.
我们需要好医生
We need a good doctor,
所以最好不是来自美洲的医生
so he better not be from America.
他可是有医疗保险的人
'Cause he has insurance.
兰迪 把医保卡给他看
Show him the card, Randy.
我能摸一下吗
Could I touch it?
不错啊 医疗保险是好的那种呢
Oh, good for you, a PPO.
就那块 我也清理过"屎"好的那种
You know, I cleaned up some PPO right there.
别闹了 这很严重
Come on, this is serious!
他可能会感染"俄方块"呢
He might have "Tetris"!
他得了受人喜爱的俄罗斯方块游戏吗
He's got the beloved Russian puzzle game?
你确定他染上的不是
Are you sure he doesn't have a case of the
超级马里奥兄弟吗
Super Mario Brothers?
前面还排有很多人呢
Well, there's a lot of people ahead of you,
麻烦你带着你男人与他的小伤伤
so why don't you take your boyfriend's boo boo
去那边坐下
and sit down?
行
Fine.
但他最好没死 因为要是他死了
But he better not die, 'cause if he does,
我要把你的那些别章
I'm gonna take those buttons
统统别到你蛋蛋上
and pin them to your sack.
不许反悔哦
Promise?
靠
Damn it!
我们估计要在这等一辈子了
I guess we're gonna be here forever.
就跟等卡洛琳洗澡的时间一样长
The exact amount of time Caroline's shower took.
所以你男人像演血腥片
Oh, so it's my fault your boyfriend
喷了我一身血 也怨我吗
Freddy Krueger-ed all over me?
卡洛琳 真的很抱歉
Caroline, I am so sorry.
没关系 兰迪
That's okay, Randy.
你可以补偿我
You can make it up to me.
就现在吧
Right now!
我刚好拿着酒水供应许可证的申请表
I just so happen to have our liquor license application,
你要不要帮忙看一下
if you want to take a look-see.
你要不要也别在那个白化猪的蛋蛋上啊 卡洛琳
Do you also want to be pinned to that albino's sack, Caroline?
伤者要来了
Okay, coming through.
我先帮你清出一条道
Okay, let me clear a path.
现在我知道我桃乐茜奶奶是什么感觉了
Now I know how my grandma Dorothy felt.
太好了 你回来了
Oh, good, you're back.
兰迪 你还好吗
Randy, are you okay?
还好
Oh, I'm fine.
你离开急诊室后 我买了点东西
Did some shopping after you left the ER.
喜欢我的新袋子吗
Like my new bag?
如果你需要手拿包来搭配
If you need a clutch to match,
我有款式类似的塑料密封袋哟
I have something similar in Ziploc.
因为那颗钉子生锈了
Because the nail was rusted
他的伤口又碰到我们的地板
and the open wound touched our floor,
医院给兰迪开了抗生素点滴
they gave Randy an IV of antibiotics.
却连一片止痛药都不给姐们儿
And not even a whisper of Vicodin for old Maxie.
麦克斯 我们总得有一个人去工作
Well, Max, one of us has to go to work
然后假装两个人都在那
and pretend both of us are there.
那肯定是你去啦
Well, it's gonna have to be you.
我不能把兰迪扔在这里
I can't leave Randy here.
这里像闹鬼的屋子 危险可是真实存在的啊
It's like a haunted house, but the dangers are real.
麦克斯 你去工作吧
Max, you're going to work.
我自己在这没事
I'll be fine here.
我曾跟西恩·潘分时使用过同一套度假屋
I had a time-share with Sean Penn.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
是我不好 害你在我家被"搞"成这样
It's my fault you got nailed in my apartment,
我要留在这里保护你
and I'm staying here to protect you.
你得去工作
You're going to work.
我一个人没事
I'll be okay.
你担心的样子真的好可爱
But you're very cute when you're worried.
就像你以为酒店没有卡通台那时一样
Like when you thought the hotel didn't get Cartoon Network.
好吧 我去
All right, fine.
但如果你要我回来 一定打给我哦
But call me if you need me to come back.
我会跟阿憨说 我在家上班
I'll tell Han I'm working the rest of my shift from home.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我刚想起我没告诉兰迪
I just remembered I didn't tell Randy
我房间有个坑
about the pothole in my bedroom.
麦克斯 别紧张
Max, relax.
我好久没看你这么紧张了
I haven't seen you this anxious
上次是因为你看不了外送披萨的进度
since the Dominos pizza tracker went down.
听着 妹子
Look, woman!
兰迪来纽约是为了看看我们有没有戏
Randy came to New York to see if our relationship could work,
但我们压根不该离开酒店
but we never should have left that hotel.
就像当你去赌城 离开繁华的长街
It's like when you go to Vegas and wander off the Strip
最终来到了居民区一样
and wind up in a residential neighborhood.
你绝对缓不过劲来
You can't come back from that.
结果我就这样在某人的棚子里住了两年
It's how I wound up living two years in someone's shed.
看来我早上发的激励内刊
I suppose the motivational newsletter
没有起到任何作用
I sent out this morning didn't do any good.
我甚至不知道我干嘛费劲出版
I don't even know why I bother publishing
《餐厅小事我"憨"你》
What's Going Han?
我喜欢那只胖松鼠的连环漫画
I like the comic strip about the fat squirrel.
那画上的是我
That picture was me!
不可能是你 人家有松果[蛋蛋]
It can't be you; he had nuts.
四号桌的女士点餐好久了
And that lady at table four ordered
她连上衣都织好穿上了 你们还没上菜
before she started knitting that sweater she's now wearing.
太好了 是兰迪
Oh, good, it's Randy.
我忘了告诉你了
Hey, I forgot to tell you,
冲完马桶五分钟内
you can't drink the tap water within five minutes
不能喝自来水
after flushing the toilet.
你能自己催吐吗
Well, can you make yourself throw up?
上菜 早餐玉米饼卷
Pickup: breakfast burrito.
兰迪打给我们的房东
Randy called our landlord
投诉钉子·帕特里克·哈里斯
to complain about Nail Patrick Harris!
我宁愿看他主持 也不愿看瑞奇·热维斯主持
I'd rather see him host something than Ricky Gervais.
我们知道 你最毒舌啦 你个死胖子
We get it: you're mean, you fat bastard.
兰迪居然打给房东了
Randy called the landlord?
但我们是非法转租客
But we're illegal subletters!
我们是非法占用者
We're squatters there!
对于大部分厕所也是
And over most toilets.
走吧 卡洛琳 我们得赶在房东到之前
Come on, Caroline, we have to get to the apartment
回到公寓
before the landlord does.
你们要走了吗
You're leaving?
中了大乐透的那个公路收费员
The tollbooth operator who won Powerball
在岗位上坚持的时间比你们更久
stayed at their job longer.
兰迪 我们得赶紧跑路
Randy, we got to go!
我来打包东西 你给栗宝装上马鞍
I'll start packing! You saddle up Chestnut.
好的 我懂规矩 一双鞋
Yeah, I know the drill: one pair of shoes,
一些你可以背着的东西
something you can carry on your back,
一顶遮阳帽 以防危地马拉的...
and a sun hat for Guatemala--
我是说 无论去哪里啦
I mean, wherever we're headed.
兰迪 你最好把剩下这点点滴喝掉
Randy, you better drink up the rest of the that IV fluid,
因为拖着那玩意跑路 会跑不快
'cause carrying that around is just gonna slow us down.
麦克斯 你这是干什么
Max, what in the hell is going on?
干嘛一惊一乍的
Why are you freaking out?
我打给房东投诉钉子
I called the landlord about a nail,
又不是打给联邦调查局举报你的护照
not the FBI about your passport...
弗兰克·德莱波特
Frank Delaport.
兰迪 我们的名字不在这房子的租约上
Randy, we're not on the lease to this apartment.
好了 我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
我需要十分钟 来给栗宝装上马鞍
I just need ten minutes to saddle up Chestnut.
正好用这时间练练我的口音
It'll give me time to practice my accent.
真是被你搞死了
We're totally screwed now.
多谢"帮忙"啊
Thanks a lot.
所以我们应该待在酒店
This is why we should have stayed in the hotel.
你可以在那里"搞死"我 我一定超享受
You could have screwed me there and I would have loved it.
麦克斯 我只是不想让你
Max, I just didn't want you
生活在地板上突出一根钉子的环境
to live with a nail sticking out of your floor,
我也知道你自己不会去处理
and I knew you wouldn't fix it yourself.
这话是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
就像你没有意识到
It's like you don't realize
你根本不用活成这样
you don't have to live like this.
太好了
Oh, great.
感觉就像跟我高中的
It's like I'm in a relationship
辅导员在谈恋爱
with my high school guidance counselor.
历史重演
Again.
你的人生可以比你想象中
You know, your life can be a whole lot better
好一百倍
than you think it can be.
你何不直接用锤子把钉子敲进去
Why don't you just hammer the nail in?
因为我们习惯了
Because we are used to it.
无视它就好了啊 就像我房间漏雨一样
We just ignore it, like the rain in my bedroom.
我就知道我的公寓对你来说太真实
I knew my apartment would be too real for you,
而现在这甚至不再是我的公寓了
and now it's not even gonna be my apartment.
好了 麦克斯
All right, Max.
我把双马鞍装上了
I put the double saddle on Chestnut,
小背包里装满了什锦干果
filled the satchel with trail mix.
那应该够咱们撑到华盛顿大桥了
That should get us to the George Washington Bridge.
你们谁都不用跑路
Nobody has to go anywhere.
那个巨型皮纳塔也不用跑
Not even your friend, the giant pinata.
-我来跟他说 -但是...
- Let me deal with this. - But...
我们从未见过房东
we've never met this guy!
我们只知道
All we know about him
就连住在2A那家伙都怕他
is that even the guy in 2A is afraid of him,
那家伙可是柯斯迪·艾黎的前夫呢
and he was married to Kirstie Alley.
我能应付得了
I can handle myself.
把我的点滴递给我
Hand me my fluids.
听上去真不爷们啊
That sounded not manly.
老兄 谢谢你赶过来
Hey, sport, thanks for coming.
他肯定谈不拢
He can't talk his way out of this.
简直是浪费时间
He's wasting his time.
他还不如试着去教肯达尔·詹娜认图形
He might as well be trying to teach shapes to Kendall Jenner.
不不 你听我说
No, no, you listen!
得 兰迪挂掉了
Well, Randy's dead.
不管我埋葬过多少男友
No matter how many boyfriends I bury,
心还是很难过啊
it's never easy.
真不敢相信我们要被这样扫地出门
I can't believe we're getting kicked out like this.
我曾幻想有一天 我买下这栋楼
In my fantasy, I bought the building
然后开一家悲剧博物馆
and opened a sadness museum.
好了 说完了
Okay, that's it.
我把房东解决了
Took care of the landlord.
你杀了他吗
You killed him?
我打给奥列格 借他朋友的皮卡
I'll call Oleg; we'll get his friend's truck
剩下的事咱们办
and take it from here.
首先我相信你们做过
Okay, first, I believe that you have
也有能力掩盖一桩谋杀
and would cover up a murder.
但没人死亡
But nobody's dead.
我只是跟他解释了一下情况
I just explained to him the situation,
你们不会被赶走
and you're not getting kicked out.
好吧 我们谁得委身于他
All right, which one of us has to marry him?
我去拿我的婚礼运动裤
I'll go get my wedding sweatpants.
我告诉他我是个律师
I just explained to him that I'm a lawyer
在他的房子里受伤了
who sustained an injury on his property.
然后我还提了电线乱接 煤气漏气
Then I mentioned the faulty wiring, the gas leak,
各种野生动物在这安家
the various wildlife living here,
最后又说了一遍 爷可是律师
and, oh-- that I'm a lawyer.
"律师"这个词能直接把人吓"屎"
The word "lawyer" makes people crap their pants.
就像法学排毒果汁 让你屎了又屎
It's like the juice cleanse of professions.
于是他免了你们俩下两个月的房租
And that is why you get the next two months rent-free,
而且把你们的名字正式加进租约
and you are now officially on the lease.
我们成了租客
We're on the lease?
我们是合法的了
We're legit?
我这辈子从未合法过
I have never been legit.
根据我的出生证明
According to my birth certificate,
我其实是一个卷心菜娃娃
I'm actually a Cabbage Patch doll.
非常感谢 兰迪
Thank you so much, Randy.
我要跟栗宝分享这个好消息
I'm gonna go tell Chestnut the good news.
栗宝
Chestnut!
怎么样
How about that?
你不用把名字改成巴勃罗了
Your new name doesn't have to be Pablo.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不知道她会怎么样
I don't know what she would have done.
她在外面可活不了
She is not made for the streets.
她甚至穿不了聚酯纤维的衣服
She's not even made for polyester.
好尴尬
This is awkward.
我在努力把一匹马弄出一扇小门
Just trying to get a horse out of a tiny doorway.
好了 起来吧
All right, up.
我得回酒店了
I have to get back to the hotel.
你看见我的防护短靴了吗
Have you seen my protective bootie?
慢着 你为什么要穿短靴回酒店
Wait, why are you taking your booties back to the hotel?
显然我待在这里让你不舒服了
Well, you're obviously not comfortable with me being here.
谁待在这里都不舒服啊
No one's comfortable being here.
这里可是个鬼地方啊
It's here.
听着 麦克斯
Look, Max.
之前我想来这里
I wanted to stay here
是因为我想看看你的生活环境
because I wanted to see how you live.
现在我知道你生活在一个专门倒印度剩菜的地方
Now I know you live on an Indian food burial ground.
好吧 你说得对
You know what? You're right.
我可以生活得更好
My life can be better.
我们还没有买锤子的钱 所以
We don't have hammer money yet, so...
你知道现在什么时间吗
You know what time it is?
锤子[行动]时间
It's hammer time!
永别了 钉子·帕特里克·哈里斯
Well, that's the end of Nail Patrick Harris.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
他的魅力如此独特 肯定跑不了
With charisma like that, he's not going anywhere.
我们顺利度过了我们第一次争吵
I think we just got through our first fight.
我们俩只有一人进了医院
And only one of us had to go to the hospital,
所以我觉得算是相当不错了
so I think that's pretty good.
我也觉得相当不错
I think that is pretty good.
你知道我还觉得什么吗
You know what else I think?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
真甜蜜
That is so sweet.
我给你俩留点私人空间
I'll give you two some privacy.
我去我房间待着
I'll be in my room.
卡洛琳
Caroline...
就算跟她一起耍白痴 你还是爆帅
Even as a mime, you're still hot.
你上班的时候 我帮你把酒水许可证的
While you were at work, I filled out your application
申请表填了
for the liquor license.
兰迪 我也爱你
Randy, I love you too.
抱歉 隔墙有耳 我在偷听
Sorry, the walls are thin, and I was listening.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
兰迪迪
And Randy. Oh...
我来拿回我的行李袋
I'm gonna need my duffle bag back.
我也不想送人了还拿回来
I hate to be an Uzbeki-giver,
但我真的很想念我的"电动"珍珠
but I really miss my vibrating pearl.
这些珍珠难道还有别的用途吗
Are these supposed to be doing other things?
别啊 那你也要把"刀"拿回去吗
Oh, no, does this mean you want your swords back?
我打算晚点用来给面包抹黄油呢
'Cause I was gonna butter some toast later.
抱歉 卡洛琳
I'm sorry, Caroline.
我们真的很想念我们的性爱玩具
We really missed our sex toys.
当我把电池塞进奥列格时 完全不够来劲儿
It's not as exciting when I just put double-A batteries in Oleg.
真是奇了怪了
That's weird.
苏菲有性爱玩具 我有男朋友
Sophie's the one with sex toys, I'm the one with the boyfriend,
而"湿嗒嗒"的却是卡洛琳
and Caroline's the one who's wet.